

Contact

Github Link: aithub.com/Qiana156

LinkedIn Profile:

linkedin.com/in/qiang156

Phone Number: (+46) 736 31 20 89

Email Address : qiang.zhang156@gmail.c

Skills

om

PHP with OOP

Git/SVN

MySQL

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Python

Django

C#

Java

IT Security

Qiang Zhang

Full-stack Developer / PHP / React / C# / Python Developer

I have worked as a Backend developer for many years and I am a good team player and can work independently. With my ability and my experiences in development, I believe that I can put myself into work and become an asset to your team quickly.

Experience

2022-05 - Full-stack developer

current Talent Match, Stockholm, Sweden

In charge of all frontend part jobs, building HR system on both Talents user and customer side by React, Creating endpoints by

Laravel, and managing data by Redux.

Implement Figma design into HTML page for colleagues. Assist DevOps in building docker files for deploying.

2022-02 - Backend developer

2022-05 Vaimo, Stockholm, Sweden

Working as a backend developer in development teams on Magento 2 to build eCommerce websites for our clients

2016-09 - Research Assistant

2020-08 Stockholm University, Stockholm, Sweden

Maintaining and developing functional modules for Global Climate

Modeling EC-Earth

Designing and Making simulation experiments with EC-Earth

Analyzing output data with Python and Shell scripts

Building website for international conference and summer course

with PHP

2014-08 - **Development Manager**

2016-02 Enke Technology co., Itd., Shenzhen, China

Developing backend API for EPOS with Workerman framework, creating basic functionalities for the project and distributing tasks

Reviewing codes and Providing support to colleagues

2007-05 - PHP Developer

2014-07 Haofeng Technology co., Itd., Shenzhen, China

Working as a full-stack programmer to develop Office Automation System which aims for realizing paperless office for our customer. I was in charge of the whole system, including frontend and backend functionalities. We use Jauery, PHP, and MySQL to build the system, use svn to manage code, and deploy it on the Linux system.

Education

2021-09 - 2022-02	System Developer Python and IT security
	Lexicon Yrkesutbildning - Stockholm, Sweden Building https://www.fun456.com with Larayel and React
	building https://www.tun456.com with Laraver and React
2014-09 - 2016-06	Atmospheric Sciences And Meteorology
	Sun Yat-sen University - Guangzhou, Guangdong Province, China

2000-09 - Bachelor of Science in Applied Mathematics

2004-06 Hengyang Normal University - Hengyang, Hunan Province, China